Oh ho oh
ho
[Music]
Flying is not only for birds [Music]
Flying is for those who have the
passion to win [Music] Passion repeat like
Taseem Come and speak to the heart [Music] Let's come and say
that those who fly with you
[Music] No
one can stop
flying [Music] This is not just a name
Staying on the ground is not our job [Music] We
go like a sport
[Music]
[Music] Whether the
path is difficult or the weather [Music] Be it bad
Samit's passion One step and then another with old age
Where is the doubt [Music] One I
One team is the identity now [Music]
This is not just a name Staying on the ground is
not our job [Music].  Like we go
[music]
This is just our name, not our land, living
[music] is not our job
[music]